# ABDUSAMAD RAIMJONOV

## FRONT-END DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT ME**

Hello everybody! My name is Abdusamad Raimjonov. I'm 20 years old. I chose this field of study because I have always been interested in programs and code, I studied at the private school "Najottalim" for 1 year. More than 50+ projects created. I am a web developer (React).

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# **VUE Developer**

Ministry Mexnat.uz | Jun 2022 - Sept 2022

- Member of "Qashqadaryo viloyat bandlik boshqarmasi" web site
- Create functional and technical applications

#### React Developer

Insource | Oct 2022 - present

- Create CRM web sites
- · Create functional and technical web sites

## **EDUCATIONAL HISTORY**

#### IT-school (Al-Khwarizmi)

Sept 2014 - May 2020

• Presidential school in Uzbekistan

#### Private school "NAJOTTALIM"

Dec 2021 - Jun 2022

• C, Python, JS, React

## **PORTFOLIO**

- https://abdusamadweb.netlify.app/
- https://github.com/abdusamadweb/

## SKILLS SUMMARY

- JavaScript ES5+, TypeScript
- React JS, React Hooks
- Redux, Redux ToolKit
- Vue, VueX, Composition API
- HTML5, CSS3/SASS/SCSS
- RESTful API, Axios
- Git | GitHub | GitLab
- BootStrap 5, MUI, Tailwind
- Responsive/Adaptive design
- WebSocket

## LANGUAGES

- Uzbek Native
- Russian Intermediate
- English Pre Intermediate

#### **CONTACT ME AT**

- +998 33 001 22 23
- abdusamadweb@gmail.com
- https://t.me/abdusamadweb
- (i) https://instagram.com/abdusamadweb